PM
oh, it's okay
I think it's very late
I fucking depressed
oh, wait, I hope it's okay
how many hours do you enjoy sweet?
ah, yeah
there is, there is
I don't know
and secondfully, I don't know
sometimes I get maybe eight hours, sometimes I get four hours
four hours, oh, and it depends
yeah
today, let's see, six
oh, not, oh, maybe I'll get
not too much
not too much, you should be
no, I can't enough
you should, you should sleep more
did you have any dinner?
you can't tell me to sleep
I didn't tell you to stay here
yeah, exactly
I wanna talk with you
yay
you kinda just thought
I was annoyed
yeah
don't eat and then do the
one, one, one, one
like I just randomly add comments
goddess, you're going nuts
yeah, I'm amazing
I'm amazing
amazing
yeah, she's my goatress
yeah
she's my goatress
yeah, yeah, she's my wife
goatress
wife goatress
I don't know how poor you are
goddess
yeah, kimoi
yeah, she's my goddess
why
oh my
oh my god
I feel like a son
I'm sorry
yes
it's okay
it's okay, it's no problem
yeah, okay